Guide to the University of Chicago, Yerkes Observatory, Office of the Director Records 1891-1946
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: 1903-1946
  - D-E, 1941, David Dunlap Observatory, 1 page Davis, Dorothy N., 5 pages DeBruycker, Irma, 1 page Dejardin, Georges, 11 pages Deutsch, Armin, 1 page Dodds, Harold W., 3 pages Dodson, Helen W., 3 pages Donnell, Dorothy, 4 pages Dornberger, W. W., 1 page Dow Chemical Company, 1 page Dunham, Theodore, 1 page Dustheimer, O. L., 1 page Easterday, M. B., 2 pages Eastman Kodak, 25 pages Ebbighausen, E. G., 23 pages Eckart, Carl, 3 pages Eckart, W. J., 3 pages Edmondson, F. K., 24 pages Eggleston, G. J. (Chicago Northwest Railroad), 2 pages Emerson, Alfred, 1 page Evans, John W., 4 pages (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - Elvey, 1941 (Box 195, Folder 1-2)
  - F, 1941, First National Bank Farnsworth, Alice H., 4 pages Fecker, J. W., 5 pages Federer, Charles E., 5 pages Fiftieth Anniversary, 1 page Flammarion, Mme. G. C., 2 pages Foccola, A., 1 page Fox, Philip, 4 pages Friend, Clarence L., 1 page (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - G, 1941, Gale, Henry Gordon, 3 pages Gamow, George, 3 pages Payne-Gaposchkin, C., 24 pages Garrett, W. H., 1 page General Education Board, 2 pages General Electric Company, (H. D. Sanborn), 2 pages Geneva Lake Home Owners Association, 21 pages Gill, Jocelyn, 8 pages Gingrich, C. H., 18 pages Gleissberg, W., 3 pages Glenn, Oliver E., 2 pages Goedicke, Victor, 6 pages Gray, Miss, 1 page Greenstein, Jesse, 34 pages Guggenheim Foundation, 2 pages (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - H, 1941, Haas, Walter, 1 page Hagemann, G., 2 pages Hagihara, Y., 8 pages Halbach, Edward A., 8 pages Hale, Mrs. G. E., 1 page Hall, John S., 14 pages Hamlin, David W., 3 pages Harper and Brothers, 2 pages Harrison, G. R., 3 pages Harvard College Observatory, 2 pages Havens, Paul Swain, 4 pages W. Heffer and Sons, 11 pages Hellweg, J. F., 5 pages Henrich, L. R., 4 pages Henyey, L., 19 pages Herget, Paul, 6 pages Herzberg, G., 5 pages Hibbard, George, 2 pages Hill, Edward L., 19 pages Hiltner, W. A., 6 pages Holmberg, Erik, 6 pages Huffer, C. M., 2 pages Hulburt, E. O., 2 pages Hynek, J. A., 19 pages (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - I-K, 1941, Illinois State Planning Committee, 10 pages Immega, T., 1 page Jahn and Olliver Janesville Gazette, 1 page Jeffers, H. M., 3 pages Jehle, Herbert, 6 pages Joy, A. H., 3 pages Judson, L. V., 2 pages Keenan, P. C., 15 pages Kent, John A., 1 page Keuffel and Esser Company, 1 page Kiess, Margaret, 2 pages King, Robert B., 2 pages Kinsley, Philip, 1 page Knox College Observatory, 1 page Kopal, A., 1 page Kopff, A., 1 page Krogdahl, Wasley, 2 pages Kreiken, V. A., 1 page (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - Kuiper, 1941 (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - L, 1941, Langmuir, Irving (GE), 2 pages Ledoux, P., 6 pages Lee, O. J., 3 pages Legion for American Unity, 3 pages Lemon, Harvey B., 15 pages Lewis, Lloyd G., 2 pages Life Magazine, 2 pages Lindblad, B. D., 1 page Linke, Walter, 2 pages Liva, H., 3 pages Lowan, Arnold N., 2 pages Lower, Harold A., 3 pages Lundmark, K., 1 page Lyttleton, R. A., 3 pages McDonald (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - M, 1941, McCuskey, S. W., 6 pages McLaughlin, Dean B., 25 pages Maidens, Frank, 2 pages Mand, Alvina, 2 pages Marchant, 4 pages Markowitz, William, 2 pages Marshak, R. E., 3 pages Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1 page Masters, L. W., 2 pages Mayall, N. U., 2 pages Meggers, William F., 11 pages Mehlin, Theodore G., 8 pages Menzel, D. H., 37 pages Millikin, R. A., 3 pages Milwaukee Astronomical Society, 8 pages Minnaert, M., 17 pages University of Minnesota Press, 1 page Missouri Kansas Texas Lines, 1 page Missouri Pacific Lines, 12 pages (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - M, 1941, Mitchell, S. A., 8 pages Monk, G. S., 14 pages Moore, J. H., 4 pages Morfford, 2 pages Morgan, W. W., 12 pages Morgenstern W. V., 2 pages Morris, C. W., 2 pages Motz, L., 3 pages Mulders, G. F. W., 2 pages Mullikin, R. S., 47 pages (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - N, 1941, Nassau, J., 13 pages National Academy of Sciences, 65 pages National Library Peiping, 2 pages National Research Corporation, 4 pages National Research Council, 4 pages Nautical Almanac Office, 1 page New York Academy of Science, 4 pages Nicholson, S. B., 1 page Northwestern Military Academy, 1 page (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - O-P, 1941, O’Keefe, John, 13 pages Olivier, C. P., 4 pages Oort, J., 1 page Oppenheimer, Harry, 7 pages Optical Society America, 5 pages Page, Leigh, 2 pages Page, Thornton, 21 pages Pearce, J. A., 7 pages Pearson, Fred, 3 pages Perkin, R. S., 3 pages Petrie, R. M., 6 pages Philosophical Society Washington, 2 pages Pierce, Newton L., 1 page Piest, O., 1 page Pitman, John H., 3 pages Plakidis, S., 2 page Plaskett, J. S., 1 page Pogo, A., 2 pages Popper, D. M., 19 pages Praeger, Richard, 3 pages Prentice-Hall, 1 page Lancaster Press, 1 page Princeton University Observatory, 3 pages Prouse, Ervin J., 4 pages (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - P, 1941, Papers published Paradox (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - Questions, 1941 (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - Questions, 1941 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - R, 1941, Rainey, Homer P., 9 pages Randers, Gunnar, 23 pages Reber, Grote, 31 pages Remington Typewriter, 1 page Reviews of Modern Physics, 5 pages Richardson, R. S., 2 pages Richtmyer, R. D., 12 pages Roach, F. E., 38 pages Rogers, F. T., 1 page Ross, F. E., 2 pages Rosseland, S., 2 pages Royal Astronomical Society, 2 pages Royal Observatory, 1 page Royal Typewriter, 7 pages Rubenstein, Pearl J., 12 pages Rudnick, Paul, 14 pages Rush, J. H., 9 pages Russell, H. N., 41 pages Russian War Relief, 4 pages (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - R-S, 1941, Reprint requests Shapley, 81 pages Swings, 89 pages (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - S, 1941, Saltykow, 2 pages Schwarschild, M., 4 pages Schenberg, M., 5 pages Schilt, Jan, 3 pages Schlesinger, Frank, 2 pages Science, 1 page Science Service, 5 pages Eastern Science Supply Company, 1 page Scientific American, 2 pages Seely, Warner, 2 pages Seyfert, Carl, 2 pages Shaw, R. William, 3 pages Sherman, Frances, 10 pages Shortley, George H., 1 page Sigma Xi, 35 pages Sitterly, C. M., 1 page Skoberla, Paul, 1 page Slipher, E. C., 1 page Smiley, Charles H., 2 pages Smith, Burke, 21 pages Society for Testing Materials, 1 page Spitzer, Lyman, 19 pages Julius Springer Verlag, 1 page Stebbins, Joel, 18 pages G. E. Stechert, 2 pages Steel Sales, 4 pages Sterne, T. E., 7 pages Stilwell, C. J., 11 pages Strand, K. A., 4 pages Suga, T., 2 pages Sullivan, F., 1 page (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - T-V, 1941, Takamine, T., 9 pages Taylor, Philip H., 3 pages Teller, Edward, 7 pages Texas and Pacific Railroad, 2 pages Thorkelson, H. J., 2 pages Todd Company, 3 pages Toniutti, Joseph, 4 pages Underwood Elliot Fisher, 1 page Unsold, A., 8 pages United States Civil Service Commission, 9 pages United States Customs, 6 pages United States Department of Commerce, 1 page United States Government Printing Office, 1 page United States Naval Observatory, 1 page United States Post Office, 4 pages Universun Book Company, 1 page Upsala Observatory, 1 page USSR Tadjik Observatory, 1 page USSR Kiev Astronomical Observatory, 2 pages Van Biesbroeck, G., 20 pages Van Biesbroeck, M., 3 pages Van den Bos, W. H., 1 page Van de Kamp, P., 3 pages Van Maanen, A., 7 pages Viking Press, 1 page Vorontsov-Velyaminov, 1 page Vyssotsky, A. N., 3 pages (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - Visitors, 1941 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - W, 1941, Wade Park Manor, 2 pages Wardman Park Hotel, 1 page Wares, G., 5 pages Warner and Swasey, 2 pages Water Safety Patrol, 2 pages Wesselink, A. J., 1 page West, Mrs. (Case), 2 pages Whipple, Fred L., 1 page Wight, Elizabeth, 4 pages Wildt, Rupert, 10 pages George Williams College, 6 pages Williams, K. (Royal Astronomical Society), 1 page Williams, Robley C., 18 pages Williamson, Ralph E., 3 pages Wilson, Edwin B., 1 page Wisconsin Commercial Organization, 9 pages Wisconsin Tel, 2 pages Wood, Fergus, 4 pages World Calendar, 10 pages World-Wide Broadcasting Foundation, 1 page Wright, W. H., 42 pages Wu, Ta-you, 9 pages Wylie, C. C., 1 page Wyse, A. B., 3 pages (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - X-Z, 1941, Young, Cyril, 1 page Zanstra, H., 10 pages Zinszer, H. A., 3 pages Zwicky, F., 1 page 50th Anniversary symposium (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - 50th Anniversary symposium, 1941 (Box 198, Folder 3-4)
  - University of Chicago Bookstore, 1941 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, 1941 (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - U, 1941, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, accident reports University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, coal University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, electric bills University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, houses (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - U, 1941, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, house 8 University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, orders (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - U, 1941, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, statements University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, bills paid University of Chicago Bursar (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - U, 1941, University of Chicago Business Manager University of Chicago Comptroller (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - U, 1941, University of Chicago Comptroller, McDonald petty cash University of Chicago Comptroller, Yerkes payroll University of Chicago Comptroller, Yerkes petty cash (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - U, 1941, University of Chicago Comptroller, McDonald payroll University of Chicago Division Office University of Chicago fellowships (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - U, 1941, University of Chicago Library University of Chicago University of Chicago notices (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - U, 1941, University of Chicago President’s office University of Chicago Filbey University of Chicago Hutchins (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago, collaboration and modernization plans, 1941 (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago Compton, 1941 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1941 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago Photo Department, 1941 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago Publicity, 1941 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - U, 1941, University of Chicago Purchasing Agent University of Chicago Registrar (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - U, 1941, University of Chicago colloquia University of Chicago reports (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - U, 1941, University of Chicago courses University of Chicago observing program University of Chicago personnel (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago requisitions, 1941 (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Mary Alexander, 1942 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - A, 1942, Astrophysical Journal, bills Astrophysical Journal, Merrill (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - A, 1942, Astrophysical Journal, finances Astrophysical Journal, reprint orders (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - A, 1942, Astrophysical Journal, subscription reports Astrophysical Journal (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - A, 1942, Abbot, C. G., 3 pages Academy of Sciences of St. Louis, 1 page Adams, C. H., (Astronomical Society of the Pacific), 6 pages Adams, W. S., 15 pages Adel, Arthur, 6 pages Air Associates, 1 page Aitken, R. G., 6 pages Aller, L. H., 12 pages American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1 page American Institute of Physics, 2 pages American Men Science, 3 pages American Museum of Natural History, 2 pages American Philosophical Society, 10 pages Anderson, F. A., 1 page Armfield, M. E., 1 page Armour Research Foundation, 3 pages Astrophysical Journal, 1 page Atkins, J. E., 2 pages Applications for positions (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - B, 1942, Babcock, H. W., 7 pages Baker, John R. (Society Freedom Science), 7 pages Baker, Robert H., 5 pages Baldwin, Ralph B., 9 pages Barton, Samuel G., 3 pages Bauer, C. A., 3 pages Bausch and Lomb, 1 page Beals, C. S., 3 pages Bidelman, W. P., 2 pages Biographical Dictionary, 1 page Biographical Encyclopedia, 1 page Blanco, Victor, 3 pages Bobrinskoy, G. V., 2 pages Bobrovnikoff, N. T., 12 pages Bok, Bart J., 54 pages Boothroyd, S. L., 3 pages Boyce, Joseph C., 4 pages Encyclopedia Britannica, 2 pages Brouwer, Dirk, 24 pages Brown, A. (Ajax Engineering), 2 pages Brown, Ross, 8 pages Brown, S. Leroy, 2 pages Broyles, Arthur A., 20 pages Bureau of Standards, 1 page Burnham Astronomical Society, 1 page Burns, Keivin, 3 pages Bush, Vannevar, 2 pages Buttrick, J. F., 1 page (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - C-D, 1942, Cambridge University Solar Physics Observatory, 1 page Campbell, Edward C., 2 pages Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh, 2 pages Carpenter, E. F., 6 pages Cattel, Ware, 3 pages Chandrasekhar, S., 10 pages University of North Carolina Library (S. F. Cockey), 1 page Collins, A. F., 4 pages Cornell, H. W., 2 pages Crew, Henry, 4 pages Critchfield, Charles L., 6 pages Crull, Harry E., 2 pages Curtis, H. D., 1 page Dartayet, Martin, 3 pages Dejardin, Georges, 3 pages Dempster, A. J., 3 pages Dempster, Richard R., 5 pages Dershem, Elmer, 25 pages Deutsch, Armin, 7 pages DeVany, A., 4 pages Dietz, Frank, 2 pages Dodson, Helen W., 4 pages Dragstedt, L. R., 1 page Draper, Glen H., 2 pages Dunham, Theodore, 1 page (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - Elvey, 171 pages, 1942 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - E-F, 1942, Eastman Kodak, 30 pages Ebbighausen, E. G., 16 pages Eckart, G., 2 pages Eddington, A. S., 2 pages Edmondson, Frank K., 14 pages Erro, L. E., 2 pages Farnsworth, A. H., 7 pages Fecker, J. W., 2 pages Federer, C. A., 18 pages Feller, W., 1 page Fish-Schurman, 1 page Foote, Harold, 1 page Freed, Simon, 2 pages Freundlich, E. F., 5 pages Fuller, C. S., 1 page First National Bank (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - G, 1942, Gale, H. G., 9 pages Gallo (postcard of telescope), 1 page Gamow, G., 10 pages Gaposchkin, Cecilia P., 27 pages Garner, Arch, 2 pages General Electric Company, 3 pages Geneva Lake Property Owners, 16 pages Gingrich, C. H., 25 pages Gleissberg, W.,1 page Goedicke, V., 3 pages Gordon, M., 2 pages Graef, Carlos, 3 pages Great Lakes Naval Training Station, 1 page Green, Louis C., 3 pages Greenstein, Jesse L., 14 pages Gronberg, A. A., 2 pages Guggenheim Foundation, 11 pages (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - H, 1942, Halback, E. A., 2 pages Hall, John S., 4 pages Hall, Marjorie, 8 pages Hall, Royal Glen, 1 page Harper and Brothers, 3 pages Harvard University Society of Fellows, 1 page Hellweg, J. F., 2 pages Henne, G., 1 page Henrich, 3 pages Henyey, L. G., 7 pages Herzberg, G., 1 page Heyden, F. J., 2 pages Hiltner, W. A., 33 pages Hodges, Paul C., 8 pages Hogness, T. R., 3 pages Hollins College, 2 pages Holmes, W. H., 3 pages Hoover, Blaine, 6 pages Horn, N. P., 3 pages Howell, H. G., 5 pages Hubble, E. P., 5 pages Huth, Carl F., 1 page Hydrographic office, 1 page Hynek, J. A., 39 pages (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - I-K, 1942, Jones, Hayden, 2 pages Joy, Alfred H., 6 pages Keenan, P. C., 10 pages Kellman, Edith, 1 page Keuffel and Esser, 1 page Klopsteg, P. E., 7 pages Knipp, J. K., 3 pages Knopf, W. C., 1 page Kopal, Z., 10 pages Kozciuszko Foundation, 3 pages Kraus, Edward H., 14 pages Krogman, W. L., 8 pages Kuiper, G. P., 66 pages (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - L, 1942, Lacroute, P., 1 page Lafayette Yodar Instrument Company, 1 page Lake Geneva Horticultural Society, 1 page Laurinburg School, 4 pages Ledousy, Alise, 1 page Ledoux, Paul, 2 pages Lee, O. J., 8 pages Leeds and Northrup, 1 page Lemon, Harvey B., 9 pages Lick Observatory, 1 page Lindblad, B., 1 page Lonngren, H. E., 2 pages Lowack, Cyril A., 3 pages Lundin, C. A. R., 2 pages Luyten, W. J., 51 pages Lyttle, Charles, 2 pages Lyttleton, R. A., 5 pages (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - McDonald, 1942 (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - M, 1942, MacLaughlin, Dean B. (American Astronomical Society), 13 pages McMath, R. R., 1 page Macmillan Company, 1 page Marchant, 7 pages Martin, W. C., 2 pages Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1 page Mathematical Institute University of Edinburgh, 1 page Mathematical Reviews, 1 page Mayall, N. U., 2 pages Menger, Karl, 6 pages Menzel, Donald, 8 pages Millikan, 1 page Milwaukee Astronomical Society, 18 pages Missouri Pacific Lines, 24 pages Mitchell, S. A., 14 pages Moore, J. H., 46 pages Morgan, W. W., 2 pages Morris, Charles, 1 page Morrison and Hughes, 1 page Morrison Hotel, 1 page Mulliken, R. S., 35 pages (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Monograph, Chandrasekhar, 1942 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - N, 1942, Nassau, J. J., 3 pages National Academy of Sciences, 36 pages National Bureau Standards, 4 pages National Research Corporation, 6 pages National Research Council, 6 pages Nautical Almanac Office, 1 page Neubauer, F. J., 4 pages Neyman, J., 4 pages Nicholson, Seth B., 9 pages Nobel Committee, 4 pages Norman, Daniel, 5 pages Nowinska, Sylvia, 9 pages (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - Navigation course at Yerkes Observatory, 1942 (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - O-P, 1942, Observatory, 1 page O’Keefe, John A., 3 pages University of Oklahoma, 2 pages Opitz, W. E., 2 pages Page, T. L., 34 pages Pan American Airways, 1 page Panofsky, H. A., 3 pages Pascal, Rose L., 2 pages Pearce, J. A., 6 pages Pearson, Fred, 3 pages Petrie, R. M., 3 pages Pettit, Edison, 5 pages Phillips, John G., 4 pages Philosophical Library, 1 page Philosophical Society of Washington, 1 page Physical Review, 1 page Pogo, A., 1 page Popper, D., 21 pages Popular Astronomy, 1 page Princeton University, 1 page Prouse, E. J., 3 pages (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - P, 1942, Papers published Paradox (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - Questions, 1942 (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - R, 1942, Reprint requests Radcliffe College, 4 pages Rainey, H. P., 14 pages Randers, Gunnar, 35 pages Reber, Grote, 3 pages Reed, Robert R., 3 pages Remington Rand, 5 pages Ridell, C., 4 pages Riggs, P. S., 1 page Roach, F. E., 25 pages Ross, R. E., 2 pages Rosseland, S., 5 pages Royal Astronomical Society, 4 pages Roy Meteorological Society, 2 pages Royal Society Edinburgh, 1 page Royal Typewriter, 3 pages Rubenstein, Pearl J., 5 pages Russell, H. N., 20 pages (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Swings, 123 pages, 1942 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - S, 1942, Shapley, 69 pages Symposium, University of Chicago (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - S, 1942, Saginaw Stamping and Tool Company, 5 pages Schilt, Jan, 3 pages Schlesinger, Frank, 1 page Schwarzschild, M., 3 pages Science, 2 pages Seares, F. H., 1 page Selective Service Board, 11 pages Shane, C. D., 3 pages Shaw, R. W., 5 pages Sieghold, Hans, 3 pages Sigma Xi, 9 pages Smiley, Charles H., 2 pages Smith, Burke, 20 pages Spitzer, Lyman, Jr., 8 pages Stalnaker, Luther, 5 pages Stebbins, Joel, 29 pages G. E. Stechert Company, 4 pages Steel, Helen R., 1 page Steel Sales, 1 page Stein, Commander, 2 pages Stephenson, R. J., 1 page Sterne, T. E., 16 pages Stetson, H. T., 1 page Stokley, James, 3 pages Stonyhurst College Observatory, 1 page Strand, K. A., 1 page Stratemeyer, G. E., 7 pages Stromberg, G., 1 page Sullivan, F. R., 1 page Swensson, John W., 5 pages (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - T-V, 1942, Tai, W. S., 2 pages Taylor, H. O., 2 pages Thackeray, A. D., 5 pages Titus, John, 3 pages Tuberg, Merle, 9 pages Tykociner, J. T., 1 page Uhler, H. S., 1 page United Press, 2 pages United States Army, 3 pages United States Civil Service Commission, 4 pages United States Government Printing Office, 1 page United States Office of Price Administration, 1 page United States Post Office, 3 pages United States Treasury, 3 pages USSR book exchange, 3 pages Van Biesbroeck, G., 26 pages Van Biesbroeck, Edwin, 2 pages Van Biesbroeck, Julia, 1 page Van Biesbroeck, Micheline, 1 page Van de Kamp, Peter, 2 pages Van Nostrand Company, 2 pages Venable, W. M., 3 pages Vosatka, Vera, 1 page Vyssotsky, A. N., 2 pages (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Visitors, 1942 (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - W, 1942, Wagman, N. E., 1 page Wares, Mabel, 2 pages Warner and Swasey, 1 page Weaver, H. F., 15 pages Wexler, Ruth, 6 pages Whipple, Fred, 47 pages Wight, Elizabeth, 6 pages Wildt, Rupert, 28 pages John Wiley and Sons, 3 pages Williams, R. C., 11 pages Williamson, Ralph, 4 pages Wilson, R. H., 2 pages Wintner, Aurel, 2 pages Wisconsin Academy of Sciences, 3 pages Wisconsin State Historical Society, 1 page Wiswell, C., 1 page Wooten, B. A., 4 pages World Calendar Association, 1 page Wright, K. O., 1 page Wright, W. H., 31 pages Wulf, Oliver, 3 pages Wylie, C. C., 13 pages Wyse, A. B., 3 pages (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - U-Z, 1942, Yale University Observatory, 1 page Zanstra, H., 2 pages Zessevitch, V. P., 1 page Zwicky, F., 2 pages University of Chicago Bookstore (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, 1942 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - U, 1942, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, bills paid University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, coal University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, houses (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - U, 1942, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, orders University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, electric bills (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - U, 1942, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, statements University of Chicago Bursar (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - U, 1942, University of Chicago Business Manager University of Chicago Comptroller (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - U, 1942, University of Chicago Comptroller, McDonald payroll University of Chicago Comptroller, Yerkes payroll University of Chicago Comptroller, petty cash McDonald University of Chicago Comptroller, petty cash Yerkes (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - U, 1942, University of Chicago navigation course University of Chicago Divisional Office (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago, Compton, 1942 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - U, 1942, University of Chicago, fellowship applications University of Chicago Library University of Chicago Press (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago Photo Department, 1942 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago reports, 1942 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - U, 1942, University of Chicago Personnel University of Chicago Publicity (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Purchasing Agent, 1942 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - U, 1942, University of Chicago Colloquium University of Chicago observing program University of Chicago requisitions (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - U, 1942, University of Chicago University of Chicago notices University of Chicago Hutchins University of Chicago Filbey University of Chicago President’s Office (Box 206, Folder 9)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Mary Alexander, 1943 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Merrill, 1943 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - Astrophysical Journal, 1943 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - A, 1943, Astrophysical Journal, bills Astrophysical Journal, reprint orders (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - A, 1943, Astrophysical Journal, finances Astrophysical Journal, subscription reports (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - A, 1943, Applications for positions Adams, C. H. (Astronomical Society of the Pacific), 4 pages Agfa Ansco, 2 pages Alien Property Custodian, 2 pages Aller, L. H., 6 pages American Association Advancement Science, 5 pages American Astronomical Society, 13 pages American Institute Physics, 2 pages American Men of Science, 7 pages American Philosophical Society, 6 pages Appel, H. M., 2 pages (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - B, 1943, Babcock, H. W., 2 pages Baker, R. H., 2 pages Baldwin, R. B., 7 pages Banerji, A. C., 2 pages Barnett, L. H., 2 pages Bauer, C. A., 42 pages Beals, C. S., 4 pages Beardsley, Niel F., 3 pages Becker and Becker, 1 page Belland, Fred, 3 pages Bennot, Maude, 6 pages Bidelman, William, 3 pages Biographical Encyclopedia of the World, 3 pages Blakiston Company, 4 pages Bobrovnikoff, N. T., 12 pages Bodine Company, 4 pages (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - B, 1943, Bok, B. J., 56 pages Boyce, R. A. M., 2 pages Bremmeman, C. E., 2 pages Encyclopaedia Britannica, 2 pages Brouwer, Dirk, 18 pages Brown, J. R., 2 pages Broyles, A. A., 35 pages Buchta, J. W., 2 pages Bunker, A. F., 1 page (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - C, 1943, Calvert, M. R., 15 pages Campbell, Leon, 2 pages Carlson, Martha B., 1 page Cattell, Ware, 2 pages Central Camera Company, 2 pages Chalonge, D., 1 page Chandrasekhar, S., 23 pages Cincinnati Astronomical Association, 1 page University of Cincinnati, 3 pages Clausing, M. E., 3 pages Cooper, C. M., 1 page Copernican Quadricentennial, 3 pages Crew, Henry, 6 pages (Box 207, Folder 9)